Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Buttons and Memorabilia Collection, 1940-1990 IBT0057
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Buttons and Memorabilia Collection
1872-2016
1940-1990
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Johnson, Cheryl
Randall, Earl
Deaner, Leo
Gormley, Regina
Moore, William (Bill)
Bartus, Norma
IBT0057
12 record cartons
1 Linear Feet 1 flatbox
This collection consists of buttons (including election buttons, dues buttons, etc.), lapel pins, keychains, watches, textiles, and other small collectible items related to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Items date from the early 1910's to the present day, with the bulk of the material dating between 1940 and 1990.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of buttons (including election buttons, dues buttons, etc.), lapel pins, keychains, watches, textiles, and other small collectible items related to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Items date from the early 1910's to the present day, with the bulk of the material dating between 1940 and 1990.
This collection consists of six significant donations from William "Bill" Moore, Norma Bartus, Earl Randall, Regina Gormley, Cheryl Johnson and Leo Deaner in addition to donations from other Teamster affiliated persons and some material acquired through purchase. Items were collected while the donors were active in the International Brotherhood of Teamsters and represent a mix of contemporary items and historic memorabilia, some of which were acquired from immediate family members of the donors.
Unique items of interest include a pair of gavels, a copper sheet etched with a letter of praise for the Teamsterettes of Topeka, Kansas, and several pins and buttons from midwestern local unions donated by Bill Moore, an organizer for IBT local union #696 for over thirty years. Also of interest are IBT conference attendee medals worn by members of the Gormley family, and a series of buttons documenting IBT activism during the late 20th century donated by Bartus.
Historical or Biographical Note
Fill
Acquistion Information
Gift of William (Bill) Moore, 13 Jan 2011, Accession 2011.047; Gift of Norma Bartus, 22 Jun 2011, Accession 2011.053; Gift of Regina Gormley; Gift of Earl Randall, Gift of Cheryl Johnson, Gift of Leo Deaner; Miscellaneous Purchases
Restrictions on Access
This collection is open for research.
Collection Organization
Organized into 7 series: Gift of Bill Moore, Gift of Norma Bartis, Gift of Earl Randall, Gift of Regina Gormley, Miscellaneous Acquistions, Gift of Cheryl Johnson and Gift of Leo Deaner.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions; Johnson, Cheryl; Randall, Earl; Deaner, Leo; Gormley, Regina; Moore, William (Bill); Bartus, Norma
- Gift of Norma Bartus, 1948-2006; 1990-2006; Series 2
  Arrangement Note
  Organized by memorabilia type; in approximate chronological order within memorabilia type.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of IBT election and activism buttons, as well as a few small items of IBT memorabilia such as keychains and pins. Items were donated by Norma Bartus.
  - Annapolis "Solidarity - Jobs and Justice" Button, 1982; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 71)
  - Support H.R. 5 & S. 55 "Gimme 5!" Buttons, 1991; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 72a-b)
  - "Restore the Right to Strike - Pass the Workplace Fairness Act" Button, 1991; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 73)
  - "Gimme Five" H.R. 5 ande S.55 Button, 1991; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 74)
  - 24th International Convention Button, 1991; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 75)
  - Support Viki Saporta Button, 1991; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 76)
  - "Stop Conway from Wrecking the American Dream" Button, 1993; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 77)
  - "Con-Way - Wrecking the American Dream" Button, 1993; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 78)
  - "Defeat NAFTA" Button, 1994; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 79)
  - "No NAFTA or New NAFTA" Button, 1994; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 80)
  - "We Deserve Higher Wages" (1994 CBC Bargaining Goal) Button, Series 2 (Box 1, Item 81)
  - "Torpedo Subcontracting" (1994 CBC Bargaining Goal) Button, Series 2 (Box 1, Item 82)
  - "Unity in 2002" Button, Series 2 (Box 1, Item 83)
  - "Si Se Puede J. Gilberto Soto" Button, 2004; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 84)
  - "Teamsters for Gephardt 2004" Button, Series 2 (Box 1, Item 85)
  - "Gephardt for Working Families" Button, 2004; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 86a-b)
  - "I.A.T.S.E. Gephardt for President" Button, 2004; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 87)
  - "Brennan 2006" Button, Series 2 (Box 1, Item 88)
  - "Petroleum Trades Union Demands Release of Hostages" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 89)
  - "I Support the US Airways Flight Attendants" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 90)
  - "Without US it's just AIR" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 91a-b)
  - "Hoffa/Flynn" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 92)
  - "CWA for Clinton/Gore" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 93)
  - "Jacobson's Peddles Pain & Misery" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 94)
  - "I Support T Joe" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 95)
  - No Lorenzo Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 96)
  - "Teamsters Women" US & Canadian Flags Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 97)
  - AFT "A Woman's Place is in Her Union" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 98)
  - "A Woman's Place is in Her Union" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 99)
  - "Teamsters Say Be American, Buy American" Buttons, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 100a-c)
  - "The New Teamsters for Good Jobs and a Better Future" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 101a-b)
  - "...And Justice for All, Even Teamsters" Buttons, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 102a-c)
  - "Workplace Fairness" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 103a-c)
  - "Campaign for Fairness AFGE 12" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 104)
  - "America Works Best When We Say... Union Yes" Buttons, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 105a-d)
  - "America Es Mejor Con La Union Diga Si" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 106)
  - "RISE - Teamsters Running a Clean Union" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 107)
  - "Harassment Poisons the Workplace" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 108)
  - "$4 a Day? No Way!" Anti-Free Trade Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 109)
  - "Teamsters Fight Drugs" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 110)
  - "Organize" School of Fish Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 111)
  - "Organizing for Power" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 112)
  - "Now More than Ever... Organize!" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 113)
  - "Special Interests Make Me Sick - National Health Insurance Now" Buttons`, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 114a-b)
  - "Diversity Matters - Human Rights Commission" Buttons, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 115)
  - "It Begins With US - Join Teamsters" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 116)
  - "Teamsters National Training" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 117)
  - "A Strong Union Involves Everyone" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 118)
  - "I Support the Best - O.P.E.I.U." Buttons, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 119a-b)
  - "OPEIU Good People Deserve a Good Contract" Buttons, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 120a-c)
  - "OPEIU This Place Works Because I Do" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 121)
  - "Job Security for a Strong American Economy" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 122)
  - "I Shouldn't Be Fired for Protecting My Job" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 123)
  - "Celebrate International Women's Day" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 124)
  - Martin Niemoller Quote/Pink Triangle Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 125)
  - "Teamsters Making the Difference for Workers" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 126)
  - "I.T.D. Wave of the Future" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 127)
  - "Go Public" USA Silhouette Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 128)
  - "Vote Teamster" Rainbow Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 129)
  - "Drive - I Vote!" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 130)
  - "I Voted for America" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 131a-b)
  - "Vote Teamster" Buttons, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 132a-b)
  - "General Drivers Union 421 Steward - Dubuque Iowa" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 133)
  - "Laboror's Internationl Union of North America, Local Union Steward" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 134)
  - OPEIU Local 2 90th Anniversary" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 135)
  - "Justice on the Job" Button, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 136)
  - "Steward" Embroidered Patch, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 137)
  - 27th IBT Convention Staff Button/Ribbon, 2006; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 138)
  - 24th International Convention Metal Plate, 1991; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 139)
  - "FLRUSH!" NOW Sticker, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 140)
  - Official Duebook of Vincent Kehoe 1948-1952, Series 2 (Box 1, Item 141)
  - "O.C.A.W. Union Yes" Keychain, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 142)
  - "You're Number 1 With Us" Local 623 (Philadelphia, PA) Keychain, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 143)
  - "Transport Workers Union N.S.W. Branch" 100 Years Coin/Keychain, Unknown; Series 2 (Box 1, Item 144)
  - "Restore the Power" Hoffa/Hogan/Young Button, 1996; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 1)
  - Hoffa/Potter 25 Member Club Button, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 2)
  - A Woman's Place is In Her Union Rosie the Riveter Button, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 3)
  - James R. Hoffa Keychain, 1971; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 4)
  - "New England Teamsters for McCarthy Vote Roy and Ray and the Team" Button, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 5)
  - "I'm a Teamster for Safety" Button, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 6)
  - "Hoffa '96 Restore the Power" Button, 1996; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 7)
  - Hoffa '96 IBT Logo Button, 1996; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 8)
  - "I'm With Hoffa" Button, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 9)
  - "I'm a Friend of Jimmy Hoffa" Button, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 10)
  - Teamsters International Convention, Las Vegas 1981 Button, Series 2 (Box 12, Item 11)
  - "Re-elect Ray Schoessling General Secy.-Treas." Button, 1981; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 12)
  - "Vote for Flynn General Secretary and Treasurer" Button, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 13)
  - Norma Bartus Staff Medal for IBT 20th Convention, 1971; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 14)
  - Local 75 Harold J. Gibbons Vice President Embroidered Patch, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 15)
  - Ron Carey "Strike Pay" Three Dollar Bill, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 16)
  - I.W. Abel (AFL-CIO President) Memorial Paperweight, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 17)
  - Jackie Presser Int'l Vice President Button, 1981; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 18)
  - "Jackie Presser" Button with Blue Ohio Ribbon, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 19)
  - Helbros Quartz Alarm Clock (?), Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 20)
  - Miami Beach, FL postcard, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 21)
  - Eastern Conference of Teamsters "Vote for the Entire Team" Button, Undated; Series 2 (Box 12, Item 22)
- Gift of Earl Randall, Series 6
  - Knights Templar 29th Triennial Conclave, San Franciso CA, 1904; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 26)
  - California Diamond Jubilee Official Souvenir Medallion and Ribbon, 1925; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 27)
  - State Federation of Labor 27th Convention in Oakland, CA Delegate Medal, 1926; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 28)
  - Golden Gate International Exposition (1939 World's Fair) Commerative Coin, Series 6 (Box 9, Item 29)
  - State Federation of Labor 42nd Annual Convention in San Francisco, CA Guest Medal, 1941; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 30a-d)
  - State Federation of Labor 42nd Annual Convention in San Francisco, CA Delegate Medal (Partial), 1941; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 31)
  - 1947 Teamsters Convention in San Francisco, CA Delegate Medal, Series 6 (Box 9, Item 32)
  - 1947 Teamsters Convention in San Francisco, CA Guest Medal, Series 6 (Box 9, Item 33)
  - Local 70 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1958) Truck-Shaped Lapel Pin, Series 6 (Box 9, Item data_value_missing_cfc3797816a07873f062c0bf0c4910c9)
  - Local 70 (Oct, Nov, Dec 1958) Lapel Pin, Series 6 (Box 9, Item 35)
  - Johnson/Humphrey Presidential Campaign Lapel Pin, 1964; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 36)
  - "LBJ for the USA" Lapel Tab, 1964; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 37)
  - "LBJ for the USA" Holographic California Button, 1964; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 38)
  - IBT 16th International Convention in Los Angeles, CA Button/Ribbon, 1952; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 39)
  - Local 70 (Oct, Nov, Dec 1965) Truck-Shaped Lapel Pin, Series 6 (Box 9, Item 40)
  - Local 70 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1966) Truck-Shaped Lapel Pin, Series 6 (Box 9, Item 41a-c)
  - Local 70 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1967) Truck-Shaped Lapel Pin, Series 6 (Box 9, Item 42)
  - "Old Time Baseball Players' Assn., Earl Platt, Metropolitan Oakland" Baseball Button, Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 43)
  - IBT Logo "Registered" Small Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 44)
  - IBT Logo Blue/White Enamel Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 45)
  - Fraternal Order of Eagles 25 Year Member Pin, Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 46)
  - Fraternal Order of Eagles 35 Year Member Pins, Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 47a-b)
  - Shriners Fez and Logo Medallion, Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 48)
  - Small Silver Plate with Decorative Border, Engraved with Number 38728; on Backside, FL&Co Maker's Mark, Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 49)
  - Bull Durham Tobacco Coin, Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 50)
  - Union Pacific Lucky Piece: "A Sample of the Aluminum in the New Union Pacific Train built by Pullman Car and MFG. Corp. ALCOA", Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 51a-b)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Ribbon Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 6 (Box 9, Item 52)
- Gift of Regina Gormley, 1913-2001; 1940-1970; Series 3
  This series consists of dues buttons, pins, and IBT conference attendee medals donated by Regina Gormley.
  - General Teamsters, Indianapolis Ind. 240 (Nov 1913) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 145)
  - General Teamsters and Chauffeurs (Dec 1916) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 146)
  - Erie System Federation No. 100 Monthly Dues (Apr 1920) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 147)
  - Teamsters and Chauffeurs, Hammond (Apr, May, Jun 1929) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 148)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Jul 1931) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 149)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Sep 1933) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 150)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Oct 1933) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 151)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Nov 1933) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 152)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Sep 1933) w/ Explanatory Note, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 153)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Jan 1934) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 154)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Apr 1934) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 155)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Aug 1934) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 156)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Dec 1934) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 157)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Jan 1935) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 158)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Mar 1935) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 159)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Apr 1935) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 160)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Jun 1935) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 161)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Jul 1935) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 162)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Nov 1935) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 163)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Dec 1935) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 164)
  - Chauffeurs and Garage Helpers 727 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1936) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 165)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Apr 1936) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 166)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Jun 1936) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 167a-b)
  - I.B.T.C.S. & H. Local 470 (Aug 1936) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 168)
  - Soda, Mineral Water, and Soft Drink Drivers and Helpers 723 (Apr, May, Jun 1937) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 169)
  - Taxi Drivers Union 777 (Jul 1937) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 170)
  - Chauffeurs, Team. & H. Union of Brockton, Mass. 653 (Jan 1938) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 171)
  - Local 493 Canton, Ill. (Jan 1938) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 172)
  - Oil Wagon Drivers, Chauffeurs, and Filling Station Employees 705 (Feb 1938) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 173)
  - Local 407 (Feb 1938) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 174)
  - Local 443 (Apr 1938) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 175)
  - Local 831 (Oct 1938) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 176)
  - Local 627 (Oct 1938) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 177)
  - Milk and Ice Cream Drivers and Employees Local 316 (Nov 1938) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 178)
  - Dairy Employees Union Local 462 (Jan 1939) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 179)
  - Local 527 (Mar 1939) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 180)
  - Chauffeurs, Teamsters & Helpers Union Milwaukee (Apr 1939) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 181)
  - Grocery, Meat & Miscellaneous Drivers Local 223 (Jun 1939) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 182)
  - Taxi Drivers Union Local 777 (Jul 1939) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 183)
  - Chauffeurs of Elmira, NY Local 529 (Jul 1939) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 184)
  - Taxi Drivers Union Local 777 (Aug 1939) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 185)
  - Wholesale, Retail Drivers, Salesmen Local 499 (Dec 1939) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 186)
  - Local 776 (Dec 1939) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 187)
  - Local 705 (Apr 1940) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 188)
  - Laundry & Dye House Drivers Union Local 712 (Apr, May, Jun 1940) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 189)
  - Beer Drivers and Helpers Local 744 (Apr, May, Jun 1940) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 190)
  - Coal Drivers, Handlers & Helpers Union Local 704 Chicago (Sep 1940) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 191)
  - Ice Men's Union Local 702 (Nov 1940) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 192)
  - Laundry & Dye House Driver's Union Local 712 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1941) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 193)
  - Local 470 (Mar 1941) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 194)
  - Local 989 (Apr 1941) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 195)
  - Coal Drivers, Helpers & Handlers Local 704 (Apr 1941) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 196)
  - Minneapolis General Drivers & Helpers Local 544 (May 1941) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 197)
  - Chauffeurs & Garage Helpers Local 727 (Oct, Nov, Dec 1941) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 198)
  - Milk Wagon Drivers' Union Local 753 (Oct, Nov, Dec 1941) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 199)
  - Beer Drivers & Helpers Local 744 (Oct, Nov, Dec 1941) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 200)
  - Local 544 (Jun 1942) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 201)
  - Laundry & Dry Cleaners Drivers Union Local 360 (Jun 1942) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 202)
  - Local 544 (Jul, Aug, Sep 1945) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 203)
  - Local 544 (Oct, Nov, Dec 1945) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 204)
  - Local 544 (Jul, Aug, Sep 1946) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 205)
  - Local 544 (Apr, May, Jun 1946) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 206)
  - Local 221 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1947) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 207)
  - Local 627 (Jun 1947) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 208)
  - Taxi Cab Drivers Union Local 777 (Apr, May, Jun 1948) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 209)
  - Local 627 (Nov 1949) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 210)
  - Local 673 (May 1953) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 211)
  - Local 632 (Sep 1953) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 212)
  - Local 673 (Oct 1953) Button, 1593; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 213)
  - Local 664 (1958) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 214)
  - Local 664 (1961) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 215)
  - Local 664 (1962) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 216)
  - Local 120 (1st Quarter 1962) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 217)
  - Local 120 (2nd Quarter 1962) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 218a-b)
  - Local 664 (1963) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 219)
  - Local 120 (4th Quarter 1963) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 220)
  - Local 664 (1964) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 221)
  - Local 120 (1st Quarter 1964) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 222)
  - Local 120 (2nd Quarter 1964) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 223)
  - Local 120 (3rd Quarter 1964) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 224)
  - Local 120 (1965) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 225)
  - Local 664 (1965) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 226)
  - Local 294 Albany & Vicinity (Dec 1965) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 227)
  - Local 120 (1966) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 228)
  - Local 664 (1966) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 229)
  - Local 710 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1966) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 230)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Local 257 (1968) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 231)
  - Local 429 Reading, PA (Apr 1968) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 232)
  - Local 671 (Apr 1968) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 233a-b)
  - Local 200 (May 1968) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 234a-b)
  - Local 676 (Jun 1969) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 235)
  - Local 334 (Aug 1968) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 236)
  - Local 823 (Aug 1968) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 237a-e)
  - Local 191 (Oct 1968) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 238)
  - Local 513 (Nov 1968) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 239)
  - Local 823 (Nov 1968) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 240)
  - Local 470 (Jan 1969) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 241)
  - Local 711 (Oct, Nov, Dec 1969) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 242a-b)
  - Local 191 (Nov 1969) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 243)
  - Construction Workers Local 13 (1970) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 244)
  - Local 664 (1971) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 245)
  - Local 120 (1971) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 246a-b)
  - Local 676 (Mar 1971) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 247a-b)
  - Local 443 (Nov 1971) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 248a-d)
  - Local 671 (Nov 1971) Buttons, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 249a-b)
  - Local 671 (Dec 1971) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 250)
  - Local 664 (1972) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 251)
  - Local 443 (Feb 1972) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 252)
  - Local 191 (Mar 1972) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 253)
  - Local 191 (Apr 1972) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 254)
  - Local 671 (Jun 1972) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 255a-b)
  - Local 671 (Jul 1972) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 256a-b)
  - Local 191 (Dec 1972) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 257)
  - Local 120 (1973) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 258a-b)
  - Local 191 (Spe 1973) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 259)
  - Local 792 (Jan, Feb, Mar 1974) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 260)
  - Local 792 (Apr, May, Jun 1975) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 261)
  - Local 421, Dubuque Iowa (Jan, Feb, Mar 1982) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 262)
  - Local 421, Dubuque Iowa (Oct, Nov, Dec 1982) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 263)
  - Local 25 (Sep 1988) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 264)
  - Local 238 (Sep 1990) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 265)
  - Local 974 Garage Maintenance and Plastic Employees (1993) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 266)
  - Local 792 (1997) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 267)
  - Local 544 (Jul, Aug, Sep 1993) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 268)
  - Local 974 (2001) Button, Series 3 (Box 1, Item 269)
  - Local 705 Button, Undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 270)
  - Local 270 New Orleans Button, Undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 271)
  - Local 320 Public and Law Enforcement Employees Union Button, Undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 272a-b)
  - A.F.L. Central Labor Union Philadelphia Button, Undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 273)
  - Teamsters Vote Crean/Gormley Slate Local 470 Button, Undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 274)
  - ALA Conference on Tax Justice, William Gormley Delegate Badge, 1969; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 275)
  - Local 362 Teamsters Logo Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 276)
  - "50 Year Member" United Brotherhood of Carpenters Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 277)
  - IBT "Drive" Lapel Pin, Undated; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 278)
  - William Gormley Delegate to the 19th IBT Convention Medal, 1966; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 279)
  - Mrs. W. Gormley Guest to the 19th IBT Convention Medal, 1966; Series 3 (Box 1, Item 280)